Roxy Harriette Grove papers, Inclusive: 1906-1953, undated, Bulk: 1930-1949, undated
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
Roxy Harriette Grove papers
Inclusive: 1906-1953, undated, Bulk: 1930-1949, undated
Baylor University, The Texas Collection http://www.baylor.edu/lib/texas/
1422
Roxy Harriette Grove, d. 1952
12 document boxes and 1 oversized box.
The Roxy Harriette Grove papers consist of correspondence, literary productions, financial papers, and teaching materials. Grove was chair of the School of Music from 1926 to 1943, when Baylor became the first school in Texas to attain membership in the National Association of Schools of Music.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Average.
Biography/Profile
Roxy Harriette Grove was born at Liberty, Missouri, about 1889. She graduated from Howard Payne College in 1906 when that school was a two-year college, and received her AB. degree from Baylor University in 1908. She later received her bachelor of music and M.A degrees from Baylor and was awarded a Doctor of Music degree from the Southern School of Fine Arts in Houston.
Grove served as a missionary to São Paulo, Brazil, from 1909 to 1912. From 1912 to 1913 she studied music under Arthur Schnabel in Germany. She taught at Howard Payne College and Hardin-Simmons University before accepting a position at Baylor in 1926. During her administration as chair of the School of Music from 1926 to 1943, Baylor became the first school in Texas to attain membership in the National Association of Schools of Music. Roxy Grove Hall at Baylor was named in her honor.
Grove was active in the Texa Association of Music Teachers, National Matthay Association of America, Mu Phi Epsilon music society, Waco Music Teachers Association, and the Waco Ensemble Club. She continued to teach music at Baylor until her death on 8 January 1952.
Scope and Content
The Roxy Harriette Grove papers consist of both personal and collected materials. The personal materials include correspondence, literary productions, financial papers, clippings, a scrapbook, and teaching materials. Most of the correspondence is between Grove and other musicians and pertains to music. Literary productions include her M.A thesis, articles, reports and music scores. The scrapbook was probably kept while she was studying under Arthur Schnabel in Germany. Collected materials consist primarily of publications from the great number of organizations with which Miss Grove was associated. These included the National Symphony Orchestra Association, National Guild of Piano Teachers, Mu Phi Epsilon, American Association of University Professors, and the National Association of Schools of Music. There are also large numbers of music catalogs in the collection which provide a good look at the music preferences during that time period.The collection also contains literary productions by other authors and composers and a large number of programs from the Baylor School of Music and the Waco Symphony Orchestra.
Arrangement
The Roxy Harriette Grove papers were partially processed prior to this arrangement. Where possible the old arrangement was kept. The papers consist of personal materials as well as collected materials such as programs, catalogs, and music scores.
Currently, the Roxy Harriette Grove papers are arranged in three series: I. Personal Materials, II Collected Materials, and III. Oversized
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to The Texas Collection in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. 1422.
Related Resources
Related references
Kelly, Dayton, ed. The Handbook of Waco and McLennan Co. Waco, TX: Texian Press, 1972.
Index Terms
Subjects (Organizations)
Baylor University -- School of Music
Places
Symphony Orchestras -- Waco -- Texas
Subjects
Baylor University -- Faculty.; Music -- Waco; Music Teachers -- Waco -- Texas
Genres
Clippings (Books, newspapers, etc.); Correspondence.; Maps.; Programs.; Scrapbooks.
- Personal Materials, 1906-1908, 1911-1912, 1921, 1927-1953, undated; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Average.
  Biography/Profile
  The Personal Materials Series consists of correspondence, invitations, sheet music and musical scores, issues of Musical America Magazine from the 1940s, postcards, financial receipts, performance programs, news clippings, photographs and prints, Grove's scrapbook from Germany, and teaching records. Some materials in Grove's teaching records are restricted. Please see the Archivist for further information.
  Index Terms
  Genres
  Photographic print; Postcards
  - Correspondence, 1921, 1934-1953, undated; 1
    - General (1 of 3), 1921, 1934-1953, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - General (2 of 3), 1921, 1934-1953, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - General (3 of 3), 1921, 1934-1953, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Classified: Edward McDowell, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Classified: Frank Reaugh, 1934-1936, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Invitations, 1934, 1945; 2
    - Invitations, 1934, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Literary Publications, circa 1930-1939, 1940, undated; 3
    - General, 1939, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Master of Arts Thesis: "Proverb Lore in Sidney", 1933 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Sheet Music and Music Scores, 1940, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Portrait Engraving Templates, 1930s (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Musical America Magazine, 1940, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Financial Papers, 1936, 1939, 1942, 1945-1950, undated; 4
    - General, 1936, 1939, 1942, 1945-1950, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Performances, undated; 5
    - Programs, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1941, undated; 6
    - General, 1941, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Photographs and Prints, undated; 7
    - Photographs and Prints (some unidentified), undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Scrapbook, 1911-1912; 8
    - Berlin, 1911-1912 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Teaching Records, 1927-1951, undated; 9
    - Notes, circa 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - General, 1927-1950 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Guides and Plans (1 of 2), 1941-1942, 1945, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Guides and Plans (2 of 2), 1941-1942, 1945, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Student Records (R), 1906-1908 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Class Notes, circa 1906-1908 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Teaching Records, 1867-1893, 1927-1950 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Class Rolls and Grades (R), 1936-1937 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Class Rolls and Grades (R), 1939-1940 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Class Rolls and Grades (R), 1941-1943 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Class Rolls and Grades (R), 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Class Rolls and Grades (R), 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Class Rolls and Grades (R), 1947 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Class Rolls and Grades (R), 1948 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Class Rolls and Grades (R), 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Class Rolls and Grades (R), 1950 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Class Rolls and Grades (R), 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Collected Materials, 1928-1929, 1932-1952, undated; 2
  This series contains music scores and lyrics, reports, clippings and Baylor School of Music materials such as programs for recitals and performances. Commencement and Baccalaureate programs, maps, and biographies on other musicians can also be found in this series. The largest section of this series deals with publications, literary productions, and catalogues from other universities, organizations and businesses selling musical scores and items. Books and lists round out this series.
  - Literary Productions, 1928-1929, 1936, 1938, 1940, 1944-1945, 1949, undated; 1
    - Music Scores and Lyrics, 1929, 1944-1945, 1949, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Music Scores and Lyrics, 1940, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Reports and Clippings (1 of 2), 1928, 1936, 1938, 1940, 1944, 1949, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Reports and Clippings (2 of 2), 1928, 1936, 1938, 1940, 1944, 1949, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Programs, 1928, 1933-1951; 2
    - Baylor School of Music (1 of 3), 1928, 1933-1935, 1938-1942, 1945-1951 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Baylor School of Music (2 of 3), 1928, 1933-1935, 1938-1942, 1945-1951 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Baylor School of Music (3 of 3), 1928, 1933-1935, 1938-1942, 1945-1951 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Baylor Commencement and Baccalaureate (1 of 2), 1937, 1939, 1942, 1945-1951 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Baylor Commencement and Baccalaureate (2 of 2), 1937, 1939, 1942, 1945-1951 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Waco Symphony Society, 1939-1946, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Other, 1926, 1934-1936, 1938-1941 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Other (1 of 2), 1942-1951, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Other (2 of 2), 1942-1951, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Maps, 1935-1936, undated; 3
    - Maps, 1935-1936, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Biographical - Musicians, 1938-1940, 1942-1943, undated; 4
    - Biographical Materials on Musicians, 1938-1940, 1942-1943, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Publications, 1932-1947, 1949-1952, undated; 5
    - Colleges and Universities: Non-Baylor (1 of 6), 1932-1933, 1936-1943, 1946, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Colleges and Universities: Non-Baylor (2 of 6), 1932-1933, 1936-1943, 1946, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Colleges and Universities: Non-Baylor (3 of 6), 1932-1933, 1936-1943, 1946, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Colleges and Universities: Non-Baylor (4 of 6), 1932-1933, 1936-1943, 1946, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Colleges and Universities: Non-Baylor (5 of 6), 1932-1933, 1936-1943, 1946, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Colleges and Universities: Non-Baylor (6 of 6), 1932-1933, 1936-1943, 1946, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Colleges and Universities: Baylor, 1937, 1941, 14943-1944, 1951-1952, circa 1932-1947 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Comprehensive Exam for B.M. Honor Graduate, 1938-1939, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Waco Symphony Orchestra, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - NBC Music Appreciation Hour, 1935-1936, 1938-1939 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - National Symphony Orchestra Association Magazine, 1939 October-December (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - National Symphony Orchestra Association Magazine, 1940 January-February (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - National Symphony Orchestra Association Magazine, 1940 March-April (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - National Guild of Piano Teachers, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - National Guild of Piano Teachers, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - National Guild of Piano Teachers, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Association of American Colleges, 1937 May, 1937 December (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Association of American Colleges, 1938 March, 1938 May (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Association of American Colleges, 1938 November, 1939 March (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Association of American Colleges, 1939 May, 1939 November (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Association of American Colleges, 1940 November (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Mu Phi Epsilon, 1943, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - American Association of University Professors, 1934 December, 1938 May (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - American Association of University Professors, 1938 October, 1938 December (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - American Association of University Professors, 1939 February, 1939 April (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - American Association of University Professors, 1939 October, 1939 December (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - American Association of University Professors, 1940 February, 1940 April (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - American Association of University Professors, 1940 June, 1940 October (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - American Association of University Professors, 1940 December, 1941 February (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - American Association of University Professors, 1949 Winter, 1950 Autumn (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - National Association of Schools of Music, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - American Matthay Association and Matthay School, 1935-1936 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - American Matthay Association and Matthay School, 1942, 1947, 1949, 1950, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - MacDowell Colony, 1944, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - New Friends of Music, Volumes I-III, 1938-1939 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Texas Association of Music Schools, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Association of Texas Colleges, Annual Meeting, 1940 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Music Teachers National Associaiton, Bulletin, 1947 Spring (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Crescendo, 1941 September, 1941 November, 1942 January (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - The Rockefeller Foundation, A Review, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Baltimore Symphony Orchestra, Twenty-Seventh Season, 1941-1942 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Proverb Lore in "The Ring and The Book," by Cornelia Marschall Smith, in the Publication of the Modern Language Association of America, 1941 March (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Seton Institute Summer School and Camp, July 1-August 25, July 15-August 25 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Camp Audubon, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - The National Association for Amerian Composers and Conductors, Annual Bulletin, 1939-1940 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - American Society of Composers, Authors, and Publishers, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Newsletter: Film Music Notes, 1942 October (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Newsletter: "Texas Music News," Texas Federation of Music clubs, vol. 26, no. 1, 1950 September (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Newsletter: "Festival News," Waco, Texas, 1945 March 25-26, 1946 March 24 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Newsletter: The Schmitz School of Piano Quarterly, 1950 November (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Catalogues, 1934-1937, 1939-1943, 1945-1948, 1950, undated; 6
    - Doblinger of Vienna, Associated Music Publishers Inc. Sellected List, undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Rental Library of Music for Symphonic Orchestra, G. Schirmer, Inc, undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Rental Library of Music for Voices and Orchestra, G. Schirmer, Inc., undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Piano Music: 20 New Editions for Piano, Music Press, Inc., undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Harcourt, Brace and Company Music Books, undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Music for Special Occasions, Primary and Secondary Music, Music Literature, Condensed History of Music, undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Operas, Operettas, and Musical Comedies from Tracy Music Library, Inc., undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Associated Music Publishers, Inc., Selected List of Classics from Augener Edition, undated (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Music and Music Literature, Augener Edition, Broude Brothers, undated (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - "Music in Library," List of Full Scores of Orchestral Works, 1940 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Music Lists, undated (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Pan-American Union-List of Latin American Music which can be purchased in the United States, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Full Orchestral Scores, Broude Brothers, Catalogue No. 25, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Reference Catalogue of Miniature Scores in Print, Broude Brothers, 1946 March (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - General Caralogue of Instrumental Music in Print, Broude Brothers, Catalogue No. 40, 1946 March (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Library of Study Scores, Masterworks from the Classic and Modern Orchestral Repertoire, Broude Brothers, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Contemporary Music, Broude Brothers, Catalogue No. 24, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Scores: Miniature, Octavio, Full, Folio, Vocal Scoresk-A Selected List, Gooseberry House, 1942 Fall (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Le Trio D'Anches De Paris (Trio of Reeds in Paris), in French, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Lists for Modern Music, Old Music, and Miniature Series, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Selected Piano Compositions for Advanced Pianists, Carl Fischer, Inc., undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Elkan-Vogel Company, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - J. Fischer & Bros., 1947 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - AM-RUS Rental Library Catalog, Leeeds Music Corporation, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Authorized American Reprints of the Classics, Associated Music Publishers, Inc., 1945-1946 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Orchestral Catalogue, Bote & Bock Publications, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Select Piano Music from the Catalog of Universal Edition-Vienna, Associated Music Publishers, undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Catalog of Music in Distinguished Editions, International Music Company, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Miniature Orchestra Scores, Universal Music Company, undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Fall Catalogue, Edwin F. Kalmus, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Antiquariats-Katalog, NR. 53, Musik, Karl Max Poppe, Leipzig C 1, undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Famous Concertos from Schirmer's Library of Musical Classics, G. Schirmer, Inc., 1941 August (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Thematic List of Edward MacDowell, Twelve Virtuoso Studies, Op. 46, undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Foreign Music Bulletin, Associated Music Publishers, Inc., 1936 October (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Ballads and Songs of Southern Michigan, University of Michigan Press, undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Eidtions Max Eschig-Paris, Associated Music Publishers, Inc., undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Guide to AMP Music, Associated music Publishers, undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Mercuiry Music, Mercury Music Corporation, undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Hawkes Pocket Scores, Ludwig Van Beethoven-Ninth Symphony, undated (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Universal Edition, Selection from the Complete Catalogue, Associated Music Publishers, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - The New Czerny, Sam Fox Publishing Co., undated (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Catalogue of Music, Charles Foley Music Publishers, undated (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - A Catalog of Two-Piano Music, J. Fisher & Bro., undated (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Catalogue of Oxford Music and Books on Music, Carl Fischer, Inc., undated (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Minstrels of the Mine Patch: Songs and Stories of the Anthracite Industry, William Salloch Books, undated (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Ballads and Songs form Ohio, William Salloch Books, undated (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Music and the Dance, Catalog No. 228, Barnes & Noble, Inc, undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Select List of the Publications of Wilhelm Hansen Copenhagen, Associated Music Publishers, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Ballads and Folksongs, William Salloch Books, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - The Annual Gamble Catalog-Supplies & New Music, Gamble Hinged Music Co., 1946-1947 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - A Catalogue of Music, Musical Literature and Scores, Broude Bros., undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - A Check-List of Miniature Scores in Print, Catalogue No. 49, Broude Bros., undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - The Longmans Descriptive Catalogue of Miniature Arrow-Scores and Musical Literature, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - History of Music, Catalogue 79, William Salloch Books, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Fall Catalogue, Edwin F. Kalmus, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - 1000 Records for College and University Libraries, RCA Victor Co., Inc., undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Music & Drama, Interesting Books, William George's Sons, LTD, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Music Library (order list), undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Scriabine Piano Works, Paraclete Music Disc, circa 1942 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - The Journal of Musicology, The Music Science Press, undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Bach Gesellschaft Publications, 1940 December 18 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - The Lyrebird Press Catalogue, The Limited Editions of the Lyrebird Press, Paris, 1936 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Concertos and Solos with Orchestra Accompaniement, L.S.U. School of Music Orchestra Library, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - The Symphonic Score Library, Marbury Books, circa 1940 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Quinto Maganini "Amerianese," Edition Musicus, Affiliated Music Corporation, undated (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - A List of Books on Musical Subjects, Edwin F. Kalmus, Publisher, undated (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - RCA Victor Record Review, The Magazine of Musical Fact and Comment, 1948 January (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - The World's Finest Musical Merchandise, Catalog No. 942, Kagan and Gaines Company, Inc., undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Catalog of Phonographic Records, Seleted titles from the Archive of American Folk Song, Library of Congress, 1943 January (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Catalog of Authentic English Decca, Odeon and Parlophone Recordings, Decca Classical Records, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - List of Books on Music, National Association of Schools of music, 1935, 1939, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Macmillan Books, 1947 Spring (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - songs from the Restoration Theater, Princeton University Press, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Science and Music by Sir James Jeans, Macmillan Company, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Philosophical Library Publications, 1947 Fall (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - The Maestro Method of Music Reproduction, Independent Music Publishers, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Creative Music Publishers, 1947 April 25 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - 66th Annual Fall Catalog of Book Bargains, Catalog No. 370, Union Library Association, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Who is Who in Music, Inc., undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Recreational Entertainment, Tracy Music Library, Inc., undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Silvio Scionti's Road to Piano Artistry, Carl Fischer, Co., undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Music Under Eight: A Book for Teachers and Parents, E.P. Dutton & Co., Inc., undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Book: Music in Institutions, Russell Sage Foundation, undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Muziekgeschiedens is Der Middeleeuwen (Music of the Middle Ages), Martinus Nihoff, Antiquarian Bookseller, undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Book: "The Yellow Bell-A Brief Sketch of the History of Chinese Music," by Chao-Mei-Pa, undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Book: Music for Fun, Whittlesey House Publications, McGraw-Hill Book Co., undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Instructional Sound Films, Erpi Picture Consultants, Inc., undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Lists: Bookcase Lists, pgs. 1-3, 6-11, undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Lists: Orders, undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Lists: University of Illinois Music Library Contents, undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Lists: Baylor Books: A Selective List of Recent Acquisitions, 1950 January 15, 1950 March 1, 1950 September 15, 1950 October 18-25, 1950 November 15, undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - List of Books for Library (Music), undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Lists: List Fragments, undated (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Oversize, 1912 August, 1918 May, undated; 3
  This series contains oversize music scores and choral pieces, either some or all handwritten by Roxy Grove. Some scores have only a few parts completed while others have full sections. Some are simply one part music. There is one print of John Phillips Sousa and one portrait of an unidentified female also in the oversize materials.
  - "Alma Mater", Chorus, undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - "Alma Mater", Male Voices, C Major, undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Baylor University "Alma Mater", undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - "The Shades of Eve", undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - "The Shades of Eve - A Cradle Song", undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - "The Shades of Eve", undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - "A Night Story", undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - "The Wood Fire", undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 8)